Guide to the Bert N. Corona Papers, 1923-1984
Department of Special Collections
- Alphabetical files, 1946-1984, Series 11
  - Chavez-Ortiz, Ricardo, Magistrate's order to release him to the custody of Bert Corona, April 19, 1972;and correspondence, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Christians for Socialism, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Christmas Songs, ditto sheets, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - CIA, in South America and Iran, clippings, 1976, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Civil Rights, Governor's Task Force, Sacramento, California, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Civil Rights, The State of Civil Rights, a report of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, February 15, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Coalition for Economic Survival, 1976, 1977, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Cobros y Cuentas de Traducciones, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Comite Bi-Nacional Mexico-U.S.A. con Trabajadores Migratorios, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - El Comité de Solidaridad del la Colonia Salvadoreña, Los Angeles, clippings and articles, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Comité de Trabajadores de Cannería y de Comida Congelada, San Jose, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Community Organizing, A Summary Outline of a Method of Organizing, by Bob Shalow, based on teachings of Cesar Chavez, October 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative, Southern California, order form for food orders, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Corman, Congressman Jim, newsletter, October 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Corona, Frank, flyer for yard work, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Cranston, Alan, Newsletter, December, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Criminal Code Bill 1630, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Crossroads, Church World Service/CROP, Pasadena, California, Water Project, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - De Ley, Margo Ynes Corona, Vitae, c.1983 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Escuela de la Raza Unida, Alternative School, Blythe, California, newspaper and flyers, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Escuela de la Raza Unida, Alternative School, Blythe, California, clippings and letters, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - EL ESPEJO, KLCS-TV 58, List of (24) programs [Films] on Hispanic Culture, March 12-June 9, 19?? (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation Dirty Tricks, clippings, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation in Mexico, clippings, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - The Film Fund Annual Report, N.Y., 1978 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Financial Research Guide to reference books on corporations, ca. 1977 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Flyers, miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - FONART, Mexican folk art store, Mexico, clipping, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - For a Society Overcoming Domination, newsletters, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Foro Nacional por la Amnistía General y la Presentación de los Desaparecidos, Culiacan, Sinaloa, Mexico, August 23-25, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Foundations, flyers and notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Gerrymandering in Los Angeles, papers, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Guadalajara, Mexico, Centros de Servicio, newsletter, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Dr. Emanuel Guerra v. Board of Trustees, subpoena to testify for Dr. Guerra, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Guide to Nationality Observances, Democratic National Committee, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Health and Welfare Legislation, California, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Hernandez, Bea, re: Bail Bonds, Bail case for Mission Foods, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Hernandez-Sanchez, Mauro Jr., visa papers and child support papers, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Hispanic Organizations, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - La Historia de Don Jacinto Trevino, Entrevista con su Hija: Agapita Trevino de Yanez, xerox, no publication, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Holguin, Veronica, employment application, June 8, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - The Hollywood Ten, clippings, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Housing Groups: Fair Housing Council of the San Fernando Valley, and CHAIN (California Housing Action and Information Network), Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Human Services Coalition, Los Angeles, 1976, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Imported Publications, Inc. 10th Anniversary Book Catalog, Fall, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Income Tax Data Sheets, for applications to operated offset machine, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Información Turística Sobre Mexico, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Institute of Cultural Affairs, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Institute of Industrial Relations, UCLA, flyers, 1979, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Instituto de Estudios Para Los Obreros, Cursos Para Los Trabajadores Sobre, Class Schedule, 1979? (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - International Study Days for a Society Overcoming Domination, list of those expected to attend, and information about the meeting planned for May 1978but postponed; Newsletters from June and July 1980 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Joint Venture Project of Northwest Valley, Pacoima, California, correspondence regarding a grant from Economic and Youth Opportunities Agency of Greater Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Kaslow, Audrey Anita Rojas, CMAA notes, August 13, 1964;Resume, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Krommer, Patricia, Resume, 1978? (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Lahman, Len, photographer and Sharon Myers, Faces Beyond the Fence, in Times-Advocate, Escondido, California, October 19, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Latino Festival, film by Image Productions, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Law Health and Welfare information, ca. 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Law School Information, ca. 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Liberty Hill Foundation, clippings and flyer on fund raising seminar, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Librería Latino América, brochures from the bookstore, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lopez, Ignacio, brochure for Stanford exhibit honoring the editor and publisher of El Espectador, May 3, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Lopez, Ignacio Lutero, Reception program, Stanford University, May 3, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Mailing list for Conference, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Marriage License Booklet, Facts About Getting Your Marriage License, Los Angeles County, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Martinez, Gerardo, letter re: medical school, July 15, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Martinez-Nateras, Arturo, Elementos Para Una Definición del Sistema Electoral Meicano, typescript, ca. 1980? (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Métodos Parlamentarios, Español, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Migrants from Texas, clipping, April 14, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Mirkin, Aurora C., bank loan papers, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - El Movimiento Estudiantil del '68, Analisis y comentarios Antecedentes, por Gilberto Guevara Niebla, in Punto Crítico, Mexico, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - El Mundo, San Jose, California, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Myths and Symbols in the Media, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - National Alliance Against Racist & Political Repression, flyers and memos, 1973-1978, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - National Catholic Reporter, [Saved for lead article, Who are the Knights of Malta?], vol. 19, no.45, October 14, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL), 1977-1981 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL), papers, clippings and flyers, 1977-1981 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - National Committee for the Self-Development of People, Abraham Reyes, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - National Conference on Religion and Labor, July 31-August 6,?? (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - National Congress of Hispanic American Citizens, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - National Land for People (NLP), Fresno, California, news sheet, 1976, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - National Security and Civil Liberties, Center for National Security Studies, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - The National Sisters Communication Service, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Nava, Julian, press releases and clippings on his bid for President of California State University, Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Nava, Julian, U.S. Ambassador to Mexico, clipping, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Necesidad De Los Consumidores Por Servicios De Salud En La Comunidad (Barrio), published by the County of Los Angeles, Public Health Commission, October 22, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Norton, Ellie and Bill, Proposal for an Activist-Oriented Symposium on the Effective Application of Liberation Theology to Ongoing Social Concerns, ca. 1980? (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Occidental College Workers, agreement with the California Teamsters Union, Local 911, 1978 through 1981;Consititution of the International Teamsters Union, 1976;Proposed Bylaws of the Western Teamsters, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Ocupación de Veracruz [in 1914] (Documentos), historical pamphlet in Spanish and English, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Office Equipment for the Center, copy machine accounts, Western Center for Immigration Studies?, 1977-1982 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Office of Migrant Services, Edmundo Velez v. Mario G. Obledo, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - ORO Development Corporation, a Farmworker Governed Community Organization, Norman, Oklahoma, Statement of Purpose, by Roberto Olivas, President, June 13, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Padres Asociados para Derechos Religiosos Educativos y Sociales, San Antonio, Texas, 1979, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Pierce Holmes Proyectos, Los Angeles, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Poetry, in Spanish, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Polaroid Land Camera order to be used for I.D. cards, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund, clippings and newsletter, 1974-75 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Population Characteristics, U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census, Persons of Spanish Origin in the United States, March 1974, March 1975, March 1978 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Press Conference Model, papers from a press conference called by Sister Patricia Krommer, Kenneth Weare, and Cynthia Anderson, re: El Salvadoran Refugee Crisis, with supporting papers, March 10, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - El Proyecto del Barrio, Inc., Public Employment and Education Center, North Hollywood, California, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Publishers Catalogues, 1975, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico, Vieques & Christians, pamphlet, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - P.U.M.A., Lompoc, California, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Raices de Sangre, by Jesus Salvador Trevino, press release, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Ramirez, Albert, Bail Bonds, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Raza Center for Alternative Education, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Reapportionment in Los Angeles, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Rebel Worker, El Ataque a La Clase Obrera, pamphlet, Obreros Rebeldes Organizados, (2) Newsletters, Oakland, California, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Special Section, Time Magazine, p.20-26, 30, 33-38, 43, February 1, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Rowe Furniture Corporation disability claim, 1977-1980 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Saint Francis Medical Center, St. Francis Fund Committee of St. Francis Province, Lynwood California, contributions to the Western Center for Immigration Studies, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Santa Anna Police Raids, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Sequin, Juan, flyer for dramatic presentation of the early Texas patriot, January 26, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Severiano M. Moreno, Musico, Maestro, Soldado, (book of music and song written for the Mexican Revolution of 1910), compiled by his grandson, Jose Luis Del Rio Moreno, privately published: Culiacan, Mexico, signed by the author, [presented to Bert Corona at Conferencia Culiacan, Mexico, 1979?],unpaged, (88 songs), 1979 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Simon, Rita, vitae, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Sistema Traduccion, Telex Communications, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Social Security Cards for members, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Songs of Justice, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research, Los Angeles, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Southwest Regional Office for the Spanish-Speaking, 1974, 1975, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Voter Registration Education Project, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Spanish-Culture Market, Profile prepared for Radio Stations KWKW and KXOR, by Forbes, Stevenson & Baldridge, January 1972. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Taxpayer Alert! Californians Against Higher Taxes, July 1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Techniques for Communicating with Spanish-Speaking Families, expenses for travel to workshop in Sacramento, July 25-26, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Theology in the Americas, meeting, articles and flyers, August 17-14, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Tourist card application for Francisco Vasquez and visa information, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Tribuna de la Juventud, simposio, September 25, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Trilateralism, by New York Circus, endorsed by the Metropolitan New York Synod of the Lutheran Church in America, February 1980 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Turismo Obrero a la U.R.R.S. 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - United Professors of California, memoranda, 1975, 1976, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - United Soviet Socialist Republics, Delegation of Soviet workers, V. Nikitin, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - United States Catholic Conference, National Conference of Bishops, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, Office of Governmental and Public Affairs, bulletins, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - United States Department of Justice, William French Smith, Attorney General, speech on intelligence gathering, December 18, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - United States Military Interventions, 1789-1945, Congressional Record, Senate, S6955, June 23, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Vargas, Adolfo, script for 28 minute Docu-drama on tuberculosis among immigrants, Por Vida, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Los Vendios, script of a play, author? first performance Elysian Park, East Los Angeles, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Volcano, Mt. St. Helens, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Services in Los Angeles County, How to Get Food and Money: The People's Guide to Welfare and other Services in Los Angeles County, by the Southern Council of Churches, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Award for Distinguished Rural Service, Sponsored by the National Rural Center, brochure, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Young, Congressman Andrew, September 8, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Your Heritage News, October 1980,Huntington Beach, California, [saved for lead article: Can (Fraternal) Organizations Save America? by Armen B. Condo, Founder, Y.H.P.A. (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - The Youth Project, Western Office, San Francisco, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Zoning notice, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Photographs, 1976; n.d., Series 12
  This series contains both dated and undated photographs of Bert Corona, Josephine Fierro, George Shibley, and Mark Day.
  - Corona, Bert, Josephina Fierro, and George Shibley, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Day, Mark, Photographs and Negatives for his publication A Charter of Rights, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Sanchez, Archbishop Robert, of Santa Fe and Senator Montoya, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Divorce Cases and Other Legal Cases, n.d., Series 13
  This series contains legal briefs, court documents, and other documents relating to cases involving Bert N. Corona.
  These case files are temporarily closed. A list of litigants are in the Collection File.
  - Legal documents (Box 47, Folder 1-26)
- Newspapers, 1970-1983, Series 14
  - ABC Tijuana, published in Mexico, 2 issues, Nov. 24, 1980-Nov. 25, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - [UPC] Advocate, published by the United Professors of California, 4 issues, [broken series], Jun. 1974-Oct. 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Beacon, published by the Unitarian Universalist Association, 1 issue, Aut. 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - The Black Panther, published by the Black Panther Party, 1 issue, May 12, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - El Bohemio, published in California, 1 issue, May 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - The California Aggie, published by the University of California at Davis, 1 issue, Jun. 23, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - California Professor, published by the Congress of Faculty Associations, 2 issues, [broken series], Feb./Mar. 1980-Oct. 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - California Teacher, published by the California Federation of Teachers, AFT, AFL-CIO, 2 issues, [broken series], Feb. 1975-Nov./Dec. 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - CED News, published in Los Angeles by the Campaign for Economic Democracy, 1 issue, Jan. 1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - C.G.T. Journal, published in Paris, 9 issues, (1 issue each for Italians, Portuguese, Algerians, Turks, and Yugoslavians, and 4 issues for the Spanish), [broken series], May 1975-Feb. 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - The [Los Angeles] Citizen, published by the Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO, 6 issues, [broken series], Oct. 7, 1977- Nov. 27, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Claridad, one is from Puerto Rico, the other two are from New York City, 3 issues, [broken series], Sept. 30, 1973-Aug. 25, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Combate, published by the Comité Seccional Universitario del Partido Comunista Mexicano, 1 issue, Jan. 15, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Common Ground (see listing with Sí Se Puede) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Compañero, published by the Partido Socialista Revolucionario, 8 issues, [broken series], Jan. 1977-Jan. 1978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Congreso de trabajo, published by the Movimiento Obrero Organizado, 2 issues, [broken series], Nov. 1978-Nov. 1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Crítica, published in Washington, D.C. by the Latin American Publishing Company, 1 issue, Dec. 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - La Crónica, The Voice of Northern Mexico, [historical paper published for use in schools?], 7 issues, Apr. 5, 1933??-Oct. 1933 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Cry for Freedom, The newspaper of poor and working people, published in New York City, 2 issues, Dec. 1978/Jan. 1979-Feb./Mar. 1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - El Cuhamil, published by the Texas Farm Workers Union, 2 issues, Apr. 25, 1977- n.d. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily Californian, published in Berkeley, CA, 1 issue, Dec. 10, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily Enterprise, Los Angeles area, 1 issue, Jan. 8, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily News, Indio and Palm Desert, CA, 1 issue, Dec. 6, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily Nexus, University of California at Santa Barbara, 1 issue, May 26, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily Pilot, Los Angeles area, 1 issue, Oct. 1, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily World, previously was the Daily Worker, 4 issues, [broken series], Nov. 13, 1975-Jun. 12, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Los Desarraigados, a collective barrio communications project of La Raza in the Midwest, 1 issue, Jul./Aug. 1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - El Día, Vocéro del Pueblo Mexicano, 1 issue, Jul. 21, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - The Dispatcher, published by the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 30 issues, [broken series], Sept. 27, 1974-Jan. 9, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - The Distributive Worker, published by the Distributive Workers of America, 18 issues, [broken series], Nov. 1975-Oct./Nov. 1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Eastside Sun, Los Angeles, CA, 1 issue, Mar. 8, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Excelsior, published in Mexico, 8 issues, [broken series], Jun. 10, 1977-Nov. 25, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Extra, published in Tijuana, Mexico, 2 issues, [broken series], May 25, 1980-Jun. 15, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - The Forumeer, published by the American GI Forum, 1 issue, Aept, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - El Gallo, La Voz De La Justicia, published in Denver, CO, 1 issue, Jan./Feb. 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - La Gente de Aztlan, published at the University of California at Los Angeles, 11 issues, [broken series], Sept./Oct. 1973-Feb. 1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - El Grafico, 1 issue, Nov. 1, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Gramma, published by the Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Cuba, 2 issues, [broken series], Nov. 18, 1973-Nov. 15, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - El Heraldo de Baja California, published in Mexico, 1 issue, Nov. 2, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Hornet, published by Fullerton College, 1 issue, Apr. 19, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - El Imparcial, published in Sonora, Mexico, 1 issue, Dec. 17, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Inciativa, published in Mexico, 1 issue, Sep. 15, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Independent Graphic News, published in Los Angeles, 1 issue, May 29, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Justicia...O?, published by La Raza Law Students at the Loyola University School of Law, 1 issue, May 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    (Chicago or Los Angeles)
  - Kadinlarin sesi, 1 issue, Aralik 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Labor Today, published by the Labor Today Associates, 3 issues, [broken series], Jan. 1974-Sep. 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Herald-Examiner, 5 issues, [broken series], Dec. 25, 1974-Aug. 4, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Times, [broken series], Nov. 25, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles Times, (3) folders, January 30, 1977-September 8, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 1,2,3)
  - Los Angeles Times, (3) folders, to December 17, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 1,2,3)
  - Los Angeles Weekly, The Publication of News, People, Entertainment, Art and Imagination in Los Angeles, 1 issue, Feb. 20-26, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - El Malcriado, published by the United Farmworkers, 3 issues, [broken series], Feb. 22, 1974-Sept. 4, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - El Mestizo, published in El Paso, Texas, Aztlan, 7 issues, [broken series], Jul. 1974-Dec. 1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - The Militant, A Socialist Newsweekly published by the Militant Publishing Association, 9 issues, [broken series], Feb. 9, 1973-Apr. 4, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Moscow News, published in Moscow by the Union of Soviet Societies for Friendship and Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, 1 issue, May 10, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Movimiento, published in Mexico by the Movimiento Revolucionario del Magisterio, 1 issue, Feb. 24, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic Reporter, published in Kansas City, MO, 1 issue, Apr. 4, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - New York Alliance, published by the Labor Community Alliance for Change, 6 issues, [broken series], Oct. 1979-Apr. 1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - New York Times, 2 issues, Aug. 21, 1977-Aug. 22, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - News Novel, published in Riverside, CA, 1 issue, Mar. 12, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - News Tribuna, published in San Francisco, CA by the Miembros de la Sociedad Interamericana de Prensa, 1 issue, Feb. 13, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Nuestra Lucha, published in Toledo, OH by the Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 10 issues, [broken series], Aug. 1976-Aug. 1979 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Open Forum, published by the American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California, 2 issues, [broken series], Nov. 1973-Sep. 1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - La Opinión, Los Angeles, 4 issues, [broken series], Sept. 23, 1976-Jul. 13, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Oposición, published by the Comité Central del Partido Comunista Mexicano, 11 issues, [broken series], Feb. 15, 1974-May 25, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Pagina Latinoamericana, published in Mexico, 3 issues, [broken series], Mar. 1980-Jun. 1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - People's World, published in San Francisco, CA, 11 issues, [broken series], Jun. 19, 1971-Oct. 3, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Plain Speaking, A News Journal of the Democratic Workers Party, 1 issue, Jun. 1-15, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - El Popo, published by MEChA and the Chicano Studies Department at the California State University at Northridge, 4 issues, [broken series], Jan. 1980- Apr./May 1981 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - [Sobotni] Prace, 6 issues, Sobota 15. dubna 1978-Sobota 22. dubna 1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)